He came again.
また来てくれた
You came again.
また来てくれたんだね
You're cute, housewife.
かわいいね、主婦ね
I wore clothes like this.
こんな感じの服を着たの
So, he came from home.
で、家から来てくれたの
I'm making it redundant.
俺が余計にしておる
At Nanpan Dobra.
ナンパンドーブラで
I was surprised, now.
びっくりしたね、今ね
This is the skirt.
これだ、スカートの
I'm hungry.
お腹減った
Extremely chilly.
肌寒暴
It's already out.
もう出ちゃった
Did you wash it?
洗った?
I washed it once.
一旦洗ったね
I was surprised.
びっくりしちゃった
I just can't stand it anymore.
ちょっと我慢できなくてさ
Why did you hide it?
何で隠しちゃったの?
Isn't it amazing?
すごくない?
Now.
今さ
I'm firing one pero right now.
ワンペロで発射してるよ、今
It was a shock, wasn't it?
衝撃だったよね
Step on it.
足踏んで
That's amazing.
すごいね
What do you feel like doing?
なんする気持ち